import { ILessonQuestion } from '../services/lesson.service';

export const VIETNAMESE_LETTER_QUESTIONS: ILessonQuestion[] = [
  {answer: 'a.m4a', lessonUnit: 'A/a', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'aw.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ă/ă', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'aa.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Â/â', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'b.m4a', lessonUnit: 'B/b', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'c.m4a', lessonUnit: 'C/c', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'd.m4a', lessonUnit: 'D/d', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'dd.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Đ/đ', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'e.m4a', lessonUnit: 'E/e', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'ee.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ê/ê', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'g.m4a', lessonUnit: 'G/g', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'h.m4a', lessonUnit: 'H/h', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'i.m4a', lessonUnit: 'I/i', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'k.m4a', lessonUnit: 'K/k', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'l.m4a', lessonUnit: 'L/l', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'm.m4a', lessonUnit: 'M/m', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'n.m4a', lessonUnit: 'N/n', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'o.m4a', lessonUnit: 'O/o', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'oo.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ô/ô', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'ow.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ơ/ơ', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'p.m4a', lessonUnit: 'P/p', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'q.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Q/q', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'r.m4a', lessonUnit: 'R/r', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 's.m4a', lessonUnit: 'S/s', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 't.m4a', lessonUnit: 'T/t', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'u.m4a', lessonUnit: 'U/u', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'uw.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Ư/ư', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'v.m4a', lessonUnit: 'V/v', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'x.m4a', lessonUnit: 'X/x', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'y.m4a', lessonUnit: 'Y/y', question: 'what-is-alphabet.m4a'},
  {answer: 'sac.m4a', lessonUnit: '/', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'quyen.m4a', lessonUnit: '\\', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'hoi.m4a', lessonUnit: '?', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'nga.m4a', lessonUnit: '~', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
  {answer: 'nan.m4a', lessonUnit: '.', question: 'what-is-character.m4a'},
];
